1. Click | Click the User Name field | Expected: Element responds as expected.
2. Fill | Enter User Name | Data: User Name: <email> | Expected: Field captures the entered data.
3. Click | Click the Password field | Expected: Element responds as expected.
4. Fill | Enter Password | Data: Password: True | Expected: Field captures the entered data.
5. Click | Click the element element | Expected: Element responds as expected.
6. Click | Click the Enter Passcode field | Expected: Element responds as expected.
7. Fill | Enter Enter Passcode | Data: Enter Passcode: 928425 | Expected: Field captures the entered data.
8. Click | Click the Verify element | Expected: Element responds as expected.
9. Click | Click the Navigator img | Expected: Navigator opened.
10. Click | Click the element element | Expected: Element responds as expected.
11. Click | Click the Invoices element | Expected: Element responds as expected.
12. Click | Click the Create Invoice button | Expected: Element responds as expected.
13. Click | Click the Create Invoice button | Expected: Element responds as expected.
14. Click | Click the element element | Expected: Element responds as expected.
15. Click | Click the FU01 US BU01 cell | Expected: Element responds as expected.
16. Click | Click the Supplier drop-down | Expected: Element responds as expected.
17. Fill | Enter Supplier | Data: Supplier: Allied Manufacturing | Expected: Field captures the entered data.
18. Click | Click the Allied Manufacturing 10001  423424234  CORPORATION option | Expected: Element responds as expected.
19. Click | Click the Number field | Expected: Element responds as expected.
20. Fill | Enter Number | Data: Number: inv22 | Expected: Field captures the entered data.
21. Click | Click the Amount field | Expected: Element responds as expected.
22. Fill | Enter Amount | Data: Amount: 100 | Expected: Field captures the entered data.
23. Click | Click the element element | Expected: Element responds as expected.
24. Click | Click the Immediate cell | Expected: Element responds as expected.
25. Click | Click the Expand Lines button | Expected: Element responds as expected.
26. Click | Click the Amount field | Expected: Element responds as expected.
27. Fill | Enter Amount | Data: Amount: 100 | Expected: Field captures the entered data.
28. Click | Click the element element | Expected: Element responds as expected.
29. Click | Click the Office Supplies cell | Expected: Element responds as expected.
30. Click | Click the Invoice Actions link | Expected: Element responds as expected.
31. Click | Click the Validate cell | Expected: Element responds as expected.
32. Click | Click the Save and Close button | Expected: Confirmation dialog is displayed.
